You look so pretty today.
تبدين جميلة جداً اليوم.
I just want to
أريد فقط أن
go out for a walk.
اخرج في نزهة.
Since you're dressed up,
بما أنك ترتدي ملابس أنيقة،
why not come with me to see my mom?
لماذا لا تأتي معي لرؤية أمي؟
Isn't this
أليس هذا
the house where I woke up?
البيت الذي استيقظت فيه؟
My mom has always lived here?
هل عاشت أمي هنا طوال حياتها؟
Then
ثم
why haven't I seen her
لماذا لم أرها؟
during this time?
خلال هذا الوقت؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
You'll see her soon.
ستراها قريباً.
I'm sure she'll like you
أنا متأكد من أنها ستعجب بك
when she meets you.
عندما تقابلك.
Why haven't you
لماذا لم تفعل ذلك؟
mentioned her before?
هل سبق أن ذكرتها؟
Should we prepare something
هل ينبغي أن نحضر شيئاً ما؟
for meeting her?
لماذا قابلتها؟
No need.
لا حاجة.
Lin Huaiwang,
لين هوايوانج
why are you doing this to me?
لماذا تفعل هذا بي؟
Did she seduce you?
هل أغوتك؟
I told you.
أخبرتك.
It has nothing to do with Zhen Yi.
لا علاقة للأمر بـ Zhen Yi.
Even if it wasn't for her,
حتى لو لم يكن ذلك من أجلها،
we would have broken up anyway.
كنا سننفصل على أي حال.
Don't leave me, okay?
لا تتركني، حسناً؟
Let go.
اتركه.
This money
هذا المال
should be enough for you to live for a while.
ينبغي أن يكون هذا كافياً لكي تعيش لفترة من الوقت.
Don't come looking for me.
لا تبحث عني.
Don't cause me any trouble.
لا تسبب لي أي متاعب.
Mo Jiao is already thirteen years old.
مو جياو تبلغ من العمر ثلاثة عشر عاماً بالفعل.
Can you really bear
هل يمكنك حقاً أن تتحمل؟
to let him grow up without a father?
أن نتركه يكبر بدون أب؟
Mom, will Dad come back?
أمي، هل سيعود أبي؟
I'm sorry, baby.
أنا آسف يا حبيبتي.
Huaiwang,
هوايوانج
why did you marry her?
لماذا تزوجتها؟
We were together first.
كنا معًا أولًا.
Is it because she's richer
هل ذلك لأنها أغنى؟
and can support your career?
وهل يمكنه دعم مسيرتك المهنية؟
I can accept that.
أستطيع أن أتقبل ذلك.
Mom,
أم،
please snap out of it.
أرجوك، توقف عن هذا الهراء.
Jiao,
جياو،
Even you despise me?
حتى أنت تحتقرني؟
Just like your dad,
تماماً مثل والدك،
you also think I'm a useless woman.
أنت تعتقد أيضاً أنني امرأة عديمة الفائدة.
Mom,
أم،
get some sleep.
احصل على قسط من النوم.
Once you fall asleep, the pain will go away.
بمجرد أن تغفو، سيزول الألم.
Mom,
أم،
since you keep saying you love me,
بما أنك تستمر في قول أنك تحبني،
do something
افعل شيئاً
meaningful for me.
هذا الأمر ذو معنى بالنسبة لي.
You killed your mom?
هل قتلت أمك؟
You're wrong.
أنت مخطئ.
She committed suicide.
انتحرت.
She wanted to die.
كانت تتمنى الموت.
What does it have to do with me?
ما علاقة هذا بي؟
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
You came here to see her, didn't you?
أتيت إلى هنا لرؤيتها، أليس كذلك؟
I'll take you to see her now.
سآخذك لرؤيتها الآن.
This is my mom.
هذه أمي.
Why are your eyes closed?
لماذا عيناك مغمضتان؟
Do you look down on my mom?
هل تحتقر أمي؟
This is my dad.
هذا والدي.
When he died,
عندما مات،
his eyes never closed.
لم تغمض عيناه أبداً.
This...
هذا...
This is Lin Moqing's mother.
هذه والدة لين موكينغ.
I should thank her.
ينبغي عليّ أن أشكرها.
If it weren't for her and her son,
لولاها ولولا ابنها،
I wouldn't be like this.
لن أكون هكذا.
You killed
لقد قتلت
all of them?
جميعهم؟
Yes.
نعم.
Is this
هذا هو
mine?
مِلكِي؟
Your acting is so bad.
تمثيلك سيء للغاية.
I should say,
أقول،
compared to Xu Meng,
بالمقارنة مع شو مينغ،
your acting is too poor.
تمثيلك سيء للغاية.
Only Xu Meng
شو مينغ فقط
deserves the elaborate way of death I've designed.
يستحق طريقة الموت المعقدة التي صممتها.
Don't hurt her.
لا تؤذيها.
Beg me.
توسل إليّ.
I beg you.
أرجوك.
Please.
لو سمحت.
Don't hurt her.
لا تؤذيها.
Please!
لو سمحت!
Your parents were smart enough
كان والداك ذكيين بما فيه الكفاية
to leave a share transfer agreement
الانسحاب من اتفاقية نقل الأسهم
that only takes effect
هذا لا يسري إلا
with your signature.
مع توقيعك.
Otherwise,
خلاف ذلك،
everything of Blue Crane
كل شيء عن بلو كرين
will be donated to charity.
سيتم التبرع بها للجمعيات الخيرية.
But they underestimated
لكنهم استهانوا بالأمر
how useless you are.
كم أنت عديم الفائدة.
Sign it!
وقّع عليه!
and I might consider letting Xu Meng go.
وقد أفكر في السماح لشو مينغ بالرحيل.
If I'm in a good mood,
إذا كنت في مزاج جيد،
I might let you two meet.
قد أسمح لكما بالالتقاء.
Still no sign of Blue.
لا يزال لا يوجد أي أثر للأزرق.
Miss Xu's whereabouts.
مكان وجود الآنسة شو.
Let me take you home first.
دعني أوصلك إلى المنزل أولاً.
Where did you go?
أين ذهبت؟
Do you know how worried I was
هل تعلم كم كنت قلقاً؟
when you suddenly disappeared?
متى اختفيت فجأة؟
I searched everywhere for you.
بحثت عنك في كل مكان.
Should I call you Lin Moqing
هل أناديكِ لين موكينغ؟
or...
أو...
Mr. Zhen?
السيد تشن؟
I saw
رأيت
the red mole on your finger before,
الشامة الحمراء على إصبعك من قبل،
but I didn't pay attention to it.
لكنني لم أعر الأمر اهتماماً.
Now I think
الآن أعتقد
everything makes sense.
كل شيء منطقي.
You've planned this scam
لقد خططت لهذه الخدعة
just for me.
فقط من أجلي.
Until the moment I woke up.
حتى لحظة استيقاظي.
Mengmeng, listen to me.
منغ مينغ، استمع لي.
What do you want to say?
ماذا تريد أن تقول؟
Keep explaining.
استمر في الشرح.
Listen to your lies. I...
استمع إلى أكاذيبك. أنا...
Actually, the first time you woke up,
في الحقيقة، في المرة الأولى التي استيقظت فيها،
I tried to tell you the truth.
حاولت أن أقول لك الحقيقة.
We just rescued Lan Hewei,
لقد أنقذنا للتو لان هيوي،
and Lin Mojiao came immediately.
وجاءت لين موجياو على الفور.
I didn't expect him to kill Lan Hewei so soon.
لم أتوقع أن يقتل لان هيوي بهذه السرعة.
By the time I got the message and arrived,
بحلول الوقت الذي وصلت فيه إلى الرسالة،
you had suffered brain damage
لقد تعرضت لتلف في الدماغ
due to prolonged lack of oxygen,
بسبب نقص الأكسجين لفترة طويلة،
and lost your memory.
وفقدت ذاكرتك.
The plan to have you impersonate Lan Hewei
الخطة هي أن تقوم بانتحال شخصية لان هيوي
[to infiltrate the Lin family for revenge]
[للتسلل إلى عائلة لين بدافع الانتقام]
[had to be terminated.]
[كان لا بد من إنهائه.]
[After that, you regained consciousness several times,]
[بعد ذلك، استعدت وعيك عدة مرات]
[but then fell back into a coma.]
[لكنه عاد بعد ذلك إلى غيبوبة.]
[Your condition was very unstable.]
[كانت حالتك غير مستقرة للغاية.]
Xu Meng.
شو منغ.
Cover your face. Who are you?
غطِ وجهك. من أنت؟
I am Mr. Zhen.
أنا السيد تشن.
Have you forgotten me?
هل نسيتني؟
Don't worry,
لا تقلق،
I won't hurt you.
لن أؤذيك.
Trust me.
ثق بي.
Xu Meng. Let me go.
شو مينغ. دعني أذهب.
Where is this place?
أين يقع هذا المكان؟
This is our home.
هذا هو منزلنا.
Honey.
عسل.
I tried all sorts of methods
لقد جربت جميع أنواع الطرق
to stimulate you,
لتحفيزك،
trying to help you recover your memory.
أحاول مساعدتك على استعادة ذاكرتك.
Your mental state was very poor at that time.
كانت حالتك النفسية سيئة للغاية في ذلك الوقت.
And
و
if you go out with this face,
إذا خرجتِ بهذا الوجه،
you will easily be targeted by Lin Mojiao.
ستكون هدفًا سهلاً لـ لين موجياو.
That would be more dangerous for you.
سيكون ذلك أكثر خطورة عليك.
What about the resort project?
ماذا عن مشروع المنتجع؟
I have already found the funding,
لقد وجدت التمويل بالفعل،
but all the partners backed out at the last minute.
لكن جميع الشركاء انسحبوا في اللحظة الأخيرة.
Was it you?
هل كنت أنت؟
You gave me shares of Yuanmeng
أعطيتني أسهمًا في شركة يوانمينغ
to confuse me,
لإرباكني،
so that I would let my guard down
حتى أتخلى عن حذري
and trust you with the project.
وأثق بك في هذا المشروع.
Lin Moqing,
لين موكينج,
you don't just want Lin Mojiao, do you?
أنت لا تريد لين موجياو فقط، أليس كذلك؟
Say it!
قلها!
You're always so eloquent.
أنت دائماً فصيح جداً.
Speak up! Are you mute?
تكلم! هل أنت أبكم؟
I admit,
أعترف بذلك،
I did use you before,
لقد تعاملت معك من قبل،
but I regret it now.
لكنني نادم على ذلك الآن.
I was blinded by hatred at that time.
لقد أعميتني الكراهية في ذلك الوقت.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Mengmeng,
مرحبًا،
can you give me another chance?
هل يمكنك أن تمنحني فرصة أخرى؟
Lin Moqing,
لين موكينج,
look at my face.
انظر إلى وجهي.
Can you tell who you are talking to?
هل يمكنك معرفة من تتحدث إليه؟
Mengmeng,
مرحبًا،
I want to see you.
أريد أن أراك.